孤儿怨：首杀
爱沙尼亚 2007年
我叫安娜·特洛耶 艺术心理治疗师
I'm Anna Troyev, the art therapy instructor.
抬手
Arms up.
应该不用每天都这样吧
I trust we won't go through this every day.
安娜?
Anna?
欢迎 准备好第一天的工作了吗
Welcome, are you ready for your first day?Hmm.
-准备好了  -这边请
- I think so. - Please.
-你住得远吗  -有点 不过值得
-Do you live far? - Uh, somewhat, but it's worth it.
我一直想用艺术去帮助人
Always wanted to use art to help people.
很好
Wonderful.
请
Please.
这边
This way.
这是我们这儿的安保程序
Those are our security procedures.
要反反复复地学习
Learn them backwards and forwards.
这儿大多数病人比较听话 但有一些...
Most of our patients are quite docile, but others--
医生 莱娜出事了
Doctor, it's Leena.
她不在房间 我们都找不到她
She's not in her room. Nobody can find her.
把房间锁上
Lock it.
莱娜是谁
Who's Leena?
这里最危险的病人
Our most dangerous patient.
就是因为她 才要你来填补这个职位空缺
In fact, she's the reason for the opening you're filling.
你之前来的那位治疗师没把她当回事
Your predecessor underestimated her
没有重视规定
and ignored protocol.
所以结局很悲催
Did not end well.
听着 不要离开这个房间
Listen to me. Do not leave this room.
别担心 这里很安全
Don't worry. You will be safe here,
一找到她 我就立马过来
and I 'll come back after we've found her.
别走...
Please, please...
你好
Hello, there.
你父母在这工作吗
Does your mum or dad work here?
我能看看你画的吗
Can I see?
这...是我？
I-- Is that me?
画得不错
That's very good.
我叫安娜 你叫什么
I'm Anna. What's your name?
莱娜
Leena.
你没回答...我之前的问题
You didn't a-- answer me before.
你父母在这工作吗
Do your parents work here?
你为什么会这么觉得
Why would you think that?
-因为你...  -我怎么了？
-Because you're-- - I'm what?
莱娜
Leena?
放下
Put it down.
莱娜 赶紧把笔放下
Leena, put it down, now.
你之前没告诉我她是个孩子
You didn't tell me she was a child.
其实她不是孩子
That's because she's not.
莱娜得了一种腺体病症
Leena suffers from a gland disorder
所以引发了成比例侏儒症
which causes, uh, proportional dwarfism,
她十岁左右时 基本上就没有再长
essentially halting her growth around age ten.
要搞清楚
Make no mistake.
莱娜也许看起来是孩子 但她其实是成年女性
Leena may look like a child, but she is a grown woman.
准确地说 她有31岁了
Thirty one, to be exact.
莱娜刚到的时候
When Leena first arrived,
挣扎着要挣脱束缚她的绑带
she struggled so hard against her restraints
因此流了很多血
that she would bleed severely.
我们也得到了教训
It was a lesson for all of us
才知道她想逃走的欲望这么强烈
on the depths of her will to be free.
莱娜早年的大部分时间
Much of Leena's early life
都在费尽心思努力活着
was spent doing whatever she could to survive.
但是她并没有长大 至少外表如此
But she never grew older, at least not on the outside.
想象一下 在你的一生中
Imagine going through your whole life,
别人只把你看作小孩
the world seeing only a child.
你绝不能把她当孩子看
It is very important that you do not see her in that way.
她一生受苦 却也利用自己的苦难
Leena uses her affliction as much as she suffers from it.
她是一个蛊惑人心的骗子
She's a exceptional con artist.
两年前 莱娜谎称自己离家出走
Two years ago, Leena wormed her way
被一户人家收留
into this family by posing as a runaway.
给她提供吃穿住宿
This family took her in. They fed her. They clothed her.
莱娜通常大肆偷窃一番就消失无踪
Normally, Leena would simply steal whatever she could
但是这次...
and then disappear, but this time,
她...
she, um...
这么说吧
Well, let me put it this way.
她现在人被关在这里
She lives here now.
伊迪
Idti.
Idti!
她总这样
She does that.
我们还有多少时间 爸爸？
How much longer have we got, Daddy?
两分钟 亲爱的
We have two minutes, darling.
小萨拉 你是想要用心记住我吗
You're learning me by heart, little Sara.
不是的爸爸 你在我心里 住在我心中
No, Daddy. I know you by heart. You're inside my heart.
我们要勇敢 是不是？
We're gonna be brave, aren't we?
是的 爸爸
Yes, Daddy.
-是的爸爸  -你好 德米特里
-Yes, Daddy. - Hello, Dmitri.
你很准时
You're on time.
很完美
It's perfect.
我自己戴不上
I can't tie these myself.
我想做点让你开心的事
I want to do something nice for you.
进来吧
You can come in.
好的 好的
Yeah. Yeah.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我爸爸不得不离开 他随时会回来的
My daddy has to go away. He'll return most any day.
我做不到
I can't do it.
我现在就能
I can do it now.
我爸爸随时可能回来
Any moment I may see my daddy coming back to me.
我爸爸不得不离开
My daddy has to go away.
伊迪 想吃糖吗
Idti, do you want some candy?
伊迪
Idti!
她把监控切断了
She cut the feed.
对不起 安娜
I'm so sorry, Anna.
希望在有新受害人之前
Hopefully, the police will find her
警察能找到她
before anyone else is hurt.
我们肯定不希望看到这样的情况
Not quite the start we had hoped for, I'm sure.
我恐怕无法胜任这个工作
This job isn't for me.
安娜
Oh, Anna.
通常来说一次就死
It usually takes only one.
不要怕 我是警察
Don't be frightened. I am police.
你的父母在哪里？
Uh, where are your parents?
他们在美国
My parents are in America.
亲...亲爱的 你叫什么
Sw-- sweetheart, what is your name?
我叫伊斯特
My name is Esther.
康涅狄格州 达里恩
击剑开始
Fence!
-太棒了  -谢谢
-Killed it. - Thanks, man.
我太为你骄傲了儿子
I'm so proud of you, sweetheart.Mm-hmm, yeah.
-没错 太棒了 小伙子  -谢谢老爸老妈
-Great job, pal. - Thanks, guys.
你大概去多久呀
How long do you think you'll be?
其实我们挺多人要一起出去玩的
Actually, a bunch of people are getting together tonight.
行吧 祝贺你儿子
Well, congrats.
那我们回家见
I'll, uh, see you guys back at the house.
难道今天我们不该家里人一起庆祝吗
I mean, this was supposed to be family night.
怎么 他总能和朋友出去玩玩吧
What, is he not supposed to have fun with his friends?
行了吧 他整天就只知道玩
Oh, God. All he does is have fun.
不啊 贡纳每天都非常刻苦
No, Gunnar works his tail off.
不是学习就是击剑
When he's not studying, he's fencing.
生活充实
He's living his life.
你别 别又胡思乱想
Don't do that. Don't go into your head.
我需要你在这里 贡纳也是
I need you to be present. Gunnar needs you.
怎么 我是刚刚没有去看儿子的比赛吗
Oh, sorry. Was I not at that match?
伊斯特不会回来了 艾伦
Esther's not coming back, Allen.
我也想她 非常想
I miss her too. I do.
每时每刻
Every moment of every day.
他在这里干什么
What is he doing here?
嗨 艾伦
Hello, Allen.
关于你的女儿伊斯特 我们有新的发现
We have an update on your daughter Esther.
俄罗斯 莫斯科
我们从伊斯特那里得到一点线索
From the little we've gotten from Esther,
我们推测是一个女人诱拐她到了俄罗斯
we believe a woman abducted her, brought her to Russia
把她当作了自己的孩子
and passed her off as her own child
后来伊斯特设法逃脱
until Esther managed to escape.
我们还没有了解到任何细节
We haven't gotten many specifics yet.
等她觉得安全了之后
Perhaps when she's feeling safer,
可能可以告诉我们更多她的经历
she can shed some more light on what she's been through.
我们给伊斯特找了一位专门的儿童心理咨询师
We have a child therapist that she'll be working with.
好的
Good.
不过她现在最需要的还是家人
What she needs right now is her family.
你要做好心理准备
Be prepared for changes.
四年过去了 孩子可能会变化很大
Four years is a long time in the development of a child.
伊斯特?
Esther?
宝贝 是我
Sweetheart, it's me.
是妈妈
It's Mommy.
能让妈妈看看你吗
Can I-- can I see you?
宝贝 是...
Sweetie, it's...
是妈妈
it's Mommy.
我以为我再也见不到你了
I thought I would never see you again.
没事了 现在都好了
Everything is right, now.
你有很长时间都没有见到我们了
It's been so long since you've seen any of us.
我找找有没有什么... 啊 这张是爸爸
Let's see if I can-- Oh, there's Daddy.
在我们的一次慈善活动上拍的
This was one of our charity events.
他那天晚上帅极了 是不是
He looked so handsome that night, didn't he?
您还需要点什么吗
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Can I grab you anything else?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
说到你哥哥
Oh, speak of the devil.
他可能已经比你记忆中又长高一英尺了
Your brother is probably a foot taller than you would remember.
这是祖母 她也对我们很好
Oh, there's Mup-Mup. She's been so good to us.
我真想早点见到她
Oh, I can't wait to see her.
不 宝贝
No, sweetie.
她过世了 你忘了吗 现在只剩下我们四个人了
She passed. Remember? It's just the four of us now.
我想上洗手间
I have to use the restroom.
洗手间在那里吗
Uh, is the restroom over there?
不 是在那边后面
No, it's just right back over there.
那后面吗
Over in the back? Oh.Mm-hmm.
-谢谢  -不客气
-Thank you. - You're welcome.
"等不及要见她了"什么蠢话
"Can't wait to see her." So stupid.
爸爸和贡纳就在楼下
Oh, Daddy and Gunnar are just downstairs.
你觉得父亲会认出我吗
Do you think Father will recognize me?
如果你不一直叫他"父亲"的话或许可以
Uh, maybe not if you keep calling him "father."
-爸爸  -没错 这好多了
-Dad. -  Yeah, that's better.
来 让我看看你
Here. Let me look at you.
我的天啊 你看起来...
Oh, my God. You look...
像个小淑女 你长大了好多
like a little lady. You've grown up so much.
把这个摘了
Take this off.
好多了 看起来没那么严肃了
That's better. It's less austere.
这是...
This is--
-抱歉  -不 我... 我才抱歉 我...
Sorry.No, I-- I'm sorry. I--
来 我们走吧
Come on. Let's go.
我感觉我好紧张
I think I'm nervous.
好了 跨一大步
All right, big step.
爸爸？
Daddy?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我不敢相信真的是你
Can't believe it's really you.
我一直都知道 我一直都知道
I always knew. I always knew.
嗨 贡纳
Hello, Gunnar.
嘿
Hey.
除了"嘿"就没了吗 我觉得你可以说点别的
I think we could do a little bit better than, "Hey."
-不是吗  -来
-Don't you think? - Come.
真高兴你回来了
Glad you're back.
我也是
Me, too.
-我们回家吧  -好
-How about we go home, huh? - Yes.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
欢迎回家 伊斯特
Welcome home, Esther.
我们保留了你房间的原貌
We left it just as it was.
我们总觉得你一定会回来的
We always knew you would come back home.
虽然你可能已经长大很多了
I mean, you've probably outgrown so much,
但我们还有好多次的圣诞节和生日礼物
but we have a lot of Christmases and birthdays
可以给你补上
to make up for,
所以你喜欢什么就告诉我们
so just let us know what you're into,
我们一定满足你
and you might get it.
-我喜欢画画  -你喜欢画画？
-I like painting. - You like to paint?
你以前从来不对画画感兴趣的
You were never interested in painting before.
这样的话 说不定你俩
Well, maybe you two
可以去你的工作室消磨点时光
can spend some time in your studio.
那再好不过了
Nothing would make me happier.
嗯 计划是这样的
So, um, plan is,
明天你要去西格医生那里 和她聊聊
tomorrow you're gonna talk to Dr. Segar.
你还记得她吗
Do you remember her?
她有一只叫西德尼的鹦鹉
She had the parrot named Sydney.Mm-hmm.
好了
Okay.
嗯 如果你还需要什么的话
Well, if you need anything...
我们就在楼下大厅 好吗
We're right down the hall, all right?
好了 你能进去了
RECEPTIONIST: Okay, you can go in.
西格医生马上就过来
Dr. Segar will be right with you.
我一会儿就要见她了
DR. SEGAR: I'm seeing her in a few minutes.
你现在就介入为时尚早 探长
I think it's too soon for you to get involved, Detective.
我想先单独和她谈谈
I'd like to talk to her alone first.
好了 我该挂电话了
Look, I have to go.
你可能想象不到
DR. SEGAR: You have no idea
能再见到你我有多开心 伊斯特
how happy I am to see you, Esther.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
天呐 你已经不是我印象中那个小姑娘了
Well, now, you're certainly not the little girl I once knew.
你现在可是个小淑女了
You're a young lady now.
你还记得我们第一次谈话时
Do you remember what I told you
我告诉过你什么吗
when we first began our sessions?
我告诉过你 要是我问了任何
I told you if I ask any questions
让你感到不自在的问题 我们就停下
that make you uncomfortable, we'll stop.
我真希望我父母也能像你一样
I wish my parents were like you.
为什么这么说
How so?
他们不停问我发生了什么
They keep asking what happened to me,
但我还没准备好告诉他们
but I'm not ready to tell them about it.
这完全没关系
DR. SEGAR: And that's perfectly fine.
我也希望你以后会跟我说
I am hoping you'll talk to me about it,
但前提是你准备好了 好吗
but only when you're ready, okay?
话虽如此
Having said that,
关于你不在家的那段时间中
is there anything you want to tell me
有什么事你想告诉我的吗
about your time away?
你想和我玩吗 西德尼
You want to play, Sydney?
我觉得西德尼好像想和我玩
I think Sydney wants to play with me.
你好 我还记得你
Hello, I remember you.
你记得我吗
You remember me?
该你了 伊斯特 你先在这里等着
DR. SEGAR: Your turn. Esther, you can wait out here.
我要跟你妈妈谈谈
I'm just going to need to talk to your mom for a moment.
-你好  -你好
-Hello. - Hi.
我喜欢你的耳环
I like your earrings.
谢谢 亲爱的
Oh, thank you, honey.
你在写什么 我很抱歉 对不起
What are you writing? Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
-没事的  -我很抱歉
-It's okay. - I'm sorry.
我去想办法清理一下
Let me go get this cleaned up.
她和你印象中的一样吗
DR. SEGAR: She seem the same as you remember?
有变化吗
Different?
她当然不一样了
Well, of course she's different.
她现在说话有口音了
DR. SEGAR: She has an accent now.
考虑到她之前一直在俄罗斯 这有问题吗
Is that unusual, considering where she's been?
也不一定
DR. SEGAR: Not necessarily.
她的语言能力还在逐步发育期间
She was there a long time when her speech
在那里待了很长时间
was still developing.
但我可以告诉你
But I will tell you, she is in far better shape
她比我想象中心智更成熟
intellectually and emotionally than I would expect.
这是好事 对吗
Well, that's good, right?
我注意到有些不对劲的地方
DR. SEGAR: I did notice some inconsistencies.
比如 她知道西德尼这个名字
For example, she said that was Sydney.
西德尼是只金刚鹦鹉
Sydney was a macaw.
有亮橘色的羽毛 比这只大四倍
Bright orange and four times the size.
但今天 她叫这只鹦鹉西德尼
Yet, today, she addressed this bird as Sydney
-而且还十分确定  -你到底想说什么
-with complete confidence. - What are you getting at?
在我看来 这像是刻意表演出来的
DR. SEGAR: To me, it felt like a performance.
他打了我 还扯坏了我的裙子
He hit me and ripped my dress!
我想回家
I want to go home.
今天就到这里吧
DR. SEGAR: That's enough for today.
好的 我们再约会诊时间
Uh, of course. We'll reschedule.
-伊斯特 你还好吗  -还好
-Esther, you all right? - Uh, yes.
嘿
Hey.
莫蒂西亚 帮我把贡纳叫过来好吗
Morticia, get Gunnar for me, would you?
-你刚刚叫我什么  -麦克 她是贡纳那个失而复得的妹妹
-What did you call me? - Mike, that's her. The sister.
妈的
Oh, shit.
我搞错了 "请"帮我叫贡纳
It's my bad. Um, get Gunnar, pozálujsta.
信不信我把你的蛋切下来喂你吃 傻逼
这是西班牙语还是什么 我没...
Is that Spanish or something? I don't--
嘿 走吧
Hey, let's go.
你妹妹真他妈是个怪人 兄弟
Your sister's a fuckin' trip, man.
搞什么 大哥 我爸还在这里呢
Seriously, dude? My dad is right there.
-我不在乎  -麦克
-I don't care. - Mike!
-妈的傻逼 - -我是谁用不着你说
-Fucking idiot. - I am what I am.
嘿 宝贝 你还好吗
Hey, honey, you okay?
-我裙子破了  -我给你买个新的
-Uh, my dress is ruined. - I'll buy you a new one.
我在想
I was thinking, uh,
咱们要不去画室
I was thinking we could go to the studio.
好啊
I would love to.
如果我不了解情况
If I didn't know any better,
我还以为你从来没来过这呢
I'd think you'd never been in here before.
好漂亮
So beautiful.
这个灯是用来干嘛的
What's the light for?
What's the light for?LEENA: Mm-hmm.
你不记得了吗 这是你老爸出名的原因
You don't remember? It's what your papa's famous for.
看这里
Here.
按一下这里
Press on this.
我一直在尝试把这么多东西放在一个画布里
Yeah, I always tried to fit so much into one canvas,
你懂吧 所以我采用了一个隐藏图层
you know? So, I resorted to a-- a hidden layer.
没有什么事是单一的 对吧
Nothing is ever just one thing, right?
好棒
So cool.
你很久没来过这里了
You haven't been in here in a while.
是 很久没来过了
No, I haven't.
这个是什么
What's this one?
别
Oh, no.
这个是...我应该把这个扔掉的
It's, uh, I should've gotten rid of this.
这...这是...这是谁？
Who-- who's-- who's that?
没必要沉溺于过去
There's no use dwelling on the past.
你回家了这就够了 对吧？
You're home now. That's all that matters, right?
我们可以一起画幅画 怎么样？
So, I was thinking we could dust off some canvasses, you know?
看看效果如何
See what comes of it.
-我很愿意  -是吗
-I would love to. - Yeah?
你想用什么画 油画笔 水彩笔
Um, what's your poison? Oil, watercolors?
-我都拿过来吧  -碳素笔
-I-- I got it all. - Charcoal?
碳素笔 可以
Charcoal? Okay.
选一个物件然后...我们坐下来
Pick an object, and-- and we'll sit down
然后我们...我们一起画
and we'll-- we'll draw it together.
我想画你
I want to draw you.
你想画我？
You want to draw me?Mm-hmm.
可以
Yeah, okay.
这还是头一次
Well, this is a first.
你想让我怎么摆造型
How do you want me?
我可以...我可以做思想者的动作
I can-- I can do The Thinker.
我想让你摆出你盯着那个看时的样子
The way you were when you were looking at that.
我不想再住在这里了
That's not a place I want to live anymore.
对
There.
就像这样
Just like that.
你在那边学的画画？
You learned to paint while you were over there?
你是只画画画 还是...还是也会...
Would you just draw, or was it-- was it also--
不是你想的那样
It wasn't what you think.
尽管发生了这么多事
It's still happening, despite everything
但依然还那样 艾伦 不 他不会在的
that's going on. Allen? No, he won't be there.
你知道他对这些事情的看法
You know how he feels about these things.
那么 明天宴会见 好吗
So, I'll see you at the gala tomorrow, then, okay?
我找你是有原因的
It's for a good cause.
贝丝 把支票本带着 和吉姆一起过来
Beth, just bring your checkbook and Jim.
为了治儿科癌症 老天爷啊
It's for pediatric cancer, for Christ's sake.
好 这样就好 谢谢你
Okay, that's better. Thank you.
我画完了
I'm finished.
这么快
Already?Mm-hmm.
-你喜欢吗  -我喜欢
-Do you like it? - I love it.
非常...非常了不起
It's-- it's incredible.
好 等我30秒 好吗
Okay, 30 seconds, all right?
让我们看看你能拿颜料做什么
And then we're gonna see what you can do with paint.
-这是我的东西  -我很抱歉
That's private.Oh, I'm sorry.
我...我看到你把它带回来了
I-- I saw that you brought it back with you.
-我觉得很特别 -你不会敲门吗
I thought it was special.You don't knock?
我在找 呃 我的金表
I was looking for, um, my gold watch.
没...没事 我相信它会自己出来的
I-- It's okay. I'm sure it'll turn up.
抱歉
Sorry.
"伊斯特的财产"
"Property of Esther."
"妈咪带我去找女巫"
"Mummy took me to Wicked."
"妈咪" 你好 妈咪
"Mummy." Hello, Mummy.
谢谢 妈咪
Thank you, Mummy.
我知道 妈咪
I know, Mummy.
妈咪
Mummy.
你们绝对想不到伊斯特有多厉害
You're not gonna believe what Esther can do.
我们在工作室呆了一下午
We spent the afternoon in the studio.
她画了一幅我的肖像
She drew a portrait of me.
她比我20多岁的时候还有才
She's got more talent than I had when I was in my 20s.
怎么可能
How's that possible?
四年前她还在画火柴人
Four years ago, she was still drawing stick figures.
-很简单  -什么
-Easy. - What?
想想你四年前都在干嘛
Think about where you were four years ago.
现在你是个击剑冠军了 好吧 就...挺佩服的
Now you're a fencing champion.Yeah, just-- It's impressive.
哪天你也给我画幅画像
Maybe you can make a portrait of me.
好好吃 妈咪
This is delicious, Mummy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
不 不 我只是...
No, no. I'm just--
你叫了谁来吗
You expecting someone?
我想我得来跟伊斯特打声招呼
I thought I'd pop in to...
看看谁来了
Look who came for a visit.
抱歉打扰你们吃晚餐了
Oh, I'm sorry to interrupt dinner.
是那位警官
This is a police officer
你失踪的时候 他帮过我们的忙
who helped us when you went missing.
他是我们的朋友
He's a friend.
伊斯特 我是来欢迎你回家的
I just, uh, came to say welcome home, Esther.
谢谢
Thank you.
我去倒杯水
Excuse me for a moment.
我得告诉你 我们的儿童心理学家觉得
You should know, um, our child psychologist feels
伊斯特应该在一个限定范围内谈她的故事
Esther should tell her story within the confines of--
而不应该是和我这样的警察谈
And not with a cop like me.
别担心 我明白这点
Don't worry. I get it.
但伊斯特之前确实从我们小镇上消失了
But Esther did vanish from our little town,
这难免让人有些担心
and that remains a concern.
我得知道这里是不是还有危险
I need to know if there's still a danger.
今天早上我和西格医生谈过了
I spoke to Dr. Segar this morning.
这么做合适吗
Is that appropriate?
她告诉我 她明天早上
She told me she's open
可以做一次集体咨询
to group discussion tomorrow morning,
来看看事情是不是都还顺利
just to see if everything's all right.
妈妈 你的慈善晚会就在明天吧
Mummy, your gala is tomorrow.
那就后天再去西格医生那吧
We'll do it the following day, then.
这很重要
It's important.
当然如果这么重要 我们肯定会去的
I mean, sure. If it's that important, we'll be there.
你忘记倒水了
You forgot to fill your glass.
伊斯特 欢迎回家
Well, uh, welcome home, Esther.
你已经说过了
You said that already.
-伊斯特  -没事 她说得对
-Esther-- - Oh, it's okay. She's right.
我送你出去吧
I'll walk you out.
真可怜 你住在这里
I'm sorry you live here.
你知道吗
Yeah.
我觉得我还是会在这里待一段时间
I think I'll stay here for a while.
我觉得西格医生那里有点问题
I think something's going on with Dr. Segar.
她好像在暗示我们 上一次见面的时候
She seemed to be implying in our last meeting
伊斯特在撒谎
that Esther is lying.
有没有搞错
That's insane.
可能她才要去看看心理医生吧
Maybe she needs to see a therapist.
对吧 我也这么觉得
I know, right?
这...你这打扮什么意思
What-- what is this?
你的约会对象
Your date.
-你也要去吗  -我当然要去了
-You're coming? - Yeah, of course I'm coming.
你是我老婆 我能帮你搞定几个有钱的讨厌鬼
You're my wife. I can deal with a few rich pricks for you.
那伊斯特怎么办
And what about Esther?
贡纳在这呢 她会好好的 对吧
Well, Gunnar's here. She'll be fine, right?
怎么了 你想让我待在家里吗
What, do you want me to stay home?
当然不是
No, no.
你知道吗 好像自从我们把伊斯特找回来了
Oh, you know, it seems like since we got Esther back,
我们俩的状态也找回来了
we got us back, too.
我再同意不过了
I couldn't agree more.
你穿戴好要多久
How long do you need to get dressed?
-我可以很快穿好  -是吗
-I can be quick. - Yeah?
我也可以很快
I can be quick, too.
不好意思 但太可爱了
I'm sorry, but they're cute.
我们把门关上就行
Let's just close the door.
把门关上吧
Just close the door.
这怎么了 不会吧
What? No. No, no, no!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你知道这裙子花了我多少钱吗
Do you know how much I spent on this dress?
-让我看看  -天呐
Let me look.Oh, man.
我可以补
I can fix that.
用一个安全别针 的确 或者用订书钉
With a safety pin.Right, or staples.
订书钉应该可以
Staples would work.
我们不在的时候 你负责照顾你妹妹
You're responsible for looking after your sister
我们相信你
while we're gone. We're trusting you, okay?
好的 爸爸 放心吧
Yeah, Dad. I got it.
你看起来真美
You look incredible.
我们走啦
We're off.
我们估计午夜才会回来
Probably won't be home until after midnight, okay?
所以别让她熬得太晚
So, don't let her stay up too late.
你有钥匙吗
You have the keys?
收到
Copy that.Hmm.
-你真好看  -谢谢你
-You look nice. - Thanks.
晚安 宝贝
Have a good night, honey.
-再见  -晚安
-Ciao. - Night.
所以我们要干嘛
So what are we going to do?
我们?
We?
就是...靠 朋友们 不好意思
Oh, it's-- Oh, shit, guys. I'm sorry.
我吸了太久了
I was holding onto it for too long.
没事的 所以 贡纳
Okay. So, Gunnar,
你妹妹是不是和你记忆中不太一样
is your sister different than you remember?
-我是说...  -你怎么想
-I mean-- - What do you think?
她去过一些东欧的性爱古拉格[原前苏联的劳改营]
She's been at some Eastern European sex gulag.
麦克
Mike.
但是 的确 她确实有些不一样了
But, uh, yeah. No, she, uh, she's different, all right.
她现在说话有点口音
She's got an accent now.
而且她穿得像丽兹·波顿一样
And she dresses like Lizzie Borden.
巨他妈诡异
It's so fucking weird.
谁是丽兹·波顿
Who's Lizzie Borden?
一个用斧头砍死父母的杀人狂
Some crazy chick who killed her parents with an axe.
嘿 伊斯特
Uh, hey, Esther,
你怎么不去看个电影之类的
why don't you, uh, go watch a movie or something?
不想看
No.
伊斯特 这不是你该来的地方
Esther, this isn't your scene.
-去看个电影吧  -滚你妈的
-Go watch a movie. - Go fuck yourself.
嘿 贡纳 我蛮喜欢她的
Hey, Gunnar, you know what? I like her.
回去吧
Go.
-管她呢 干杯  -干杯
-Anyway, cheers! - Cheers.
耶 我要喝个烂醉
Yeah. I'll fucking drink to that.
呃 我们刚刚说什么来着
Um, what we were talking about?
谁在敲门
Who's that?
晚上好
Evening.
嘿 我父母不在家 他们去参加我妈妈的宴会了
Hey, my parents aren't here. They're at Mom's gala.
-那算我走运  -是啊
-Just my luck. - Yeah.
你们在开派对吗
Having a party?
没有 就是几个朋友
No, it's just a few friends.
街上都能闻到大麻的味儿
Smell the weed from the street.
什么 呃 我不知道...
What? Um, I don't know--
我不知道你在说些什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
听着 这里什么都没发生 好吗
Um, look, nothing's going on here, okay?
这样 我会告诉我父母你来过
So um, why don't I just tell my parents
其余一切就当没发生过
that you stopped by, and we can just forget all about this.
可以吗
Cool?
-可以  -很好
-Cool. - Good.
我走之前能用一下洗手间吗
You mind if I hit the restroom before I go?
当然 当然
Yeah, whatever. Yeah, sure.
今晚可太成功了
That was a blast.
难怪那些一毛不拔的百万富翁都要排着队
No wonder those uptight millionaires line up
来给基金会捐款
to give the foundation money.
不 主要是酒精的作用
Oh, no. It's the booze.
不是因为酒精 宝贝
It's not the booze, hon.
是主办方
It's the host.
你总是能把别人最好的一面激发出来
You bring the best out of people.
我只希望我们的房子还能完完整整的
I just hope the house is still standing.
我16岁的时候 差点...
I mean, when I was 16, I-- I nearly...
差点把房子给烧了
...I nearly burnt the house down.
放心吧 贡纳不会这么做的
No, Gunnar would never do that.
我说的可不是贡纳
Who says I'm talking about Gunnar?
伊斯特 我们回来了
Esther, we're home.
伊斯特?
Esther?
"萨朗精神病院"？
"Saarne Institute?"
伊斯特?
Esther?
如果你不是伊斯特的话 那你到底是谁？
If you're not Esther, who the hell are you?
你怎么知道我不是伊斯特
How did you know that I'm not Esther?
甚至连她自己的妈妈都不知道
Her own mother doesn't even know.
你错了孩子 她知道
Yeah, kid, she does.
靠
Damn it.
妈妈？
Mummy?
你他妈在看什么
The fuck are you looking at?
我就直说了
So, let me get this straight.
你是一个成年女人 并且还是一个通缉犯 是吧
You're a grown-ass woman and a wanted criminal?
这也太操蛋了
That is beyond fucked up.
对了 这就是我一辈子都在做的事
This is all I ever do anymore, by the way.
替我的孩子收拾残局
Clean up after my kids.
别担心 妈妈会搞定的
Don't worry about it. Mommy'll take care of it.
妈妈总能搞定一切
Mommy takes care of everything.
贡纳说唐南来过家里的时候
When Gunnar told me Donnan came to the house,
我就知道我能在这里找到你
I knew I'd find you here.
你本来可以从我们这骗得一大笔钱
You could have robbed us blind and disappeared
然后一有机会就销声匿迹 但你并没有
the second you had a chance, but you didn't.
为什么
Why is that?
你在下一盘大棋 对吗 扮演乖女儿的角色 操控着我们
You're thinking bigger, right? Play the part, manipulate us,
一年后我们就会遇到一些悲惨的事故
and a year from now we meet with some tragic accident.
我猜对了吗
Am I getting warm?
让我走 我保证你不会再见到我
Let me go. You'll never see me again.
这才是我所害怕的事情
That's exactly what I'm afraid of.
我们不能让伊斯特失踪两次 对吧
We can't have Esther disappear twice now, can we?
她不是失踪的
She didn't disappear.
当时我什么都做不了
There was nothing that I could do for her,
一切都为时已晚
it was too late.
贡纳对她一直都很粗暴
Gunnar, he was always way too rough with her.
那天晚上他下手重了 我又能做些什么呢
That night he just went too far. What was I supposed to do?
因为兄妹之间过火的打闹
Hand over the only child I had left over some
就把我唯一的孩子交出去吗
sibling bullshit that went too far?
我全心全意地爱着我的女儿
I loved my daughter with all my heart,
无论发生什么 一位母亲总会选择保护她的家人
but a mother protects her family, no matter what,
如果你觉得我会允许一个精神病侏儒
and if you think... ...that I'm going to let some
把我现在拥有的一切全都摧毁
psycho dwarf destroy what I have built...
那你想多了
you're mistaken.
我们美国人的祖先当年乘着他妈的五月花号
This family came over on the fucking Mayflower
远渡重洋来这里建立了新国度 我们很重要 艾伦很重要
and built this country. We matter. Allen matters.
当他知道伊斯特还活着的时候
When he got the news Esther was alive,
他脸上的笑容... 我一定得把这事做到底
the happiness on his face, I had to make this work.
艾伦还不知道伊斯特身上到底发生了什么
Allen doesn't know what happened to Esther.
而你要帮我确保他永远不会发现
And you are gonna help me make sure that he never does.
天底下只有一件事比死去的孩子更可怕
There's only one thing worse than the death of a child,
那就是失踪的孩子
and that is a child who is missing.
伊斯特失踪后 艾伦完全变了
Esther's disappearance changed Allen,
变得不像他本人 完全没有他该有的样子
changed who he was, who he is supposed to be,
但你就是答案
but you are the answer.
你和我有机会把这烂摊子
You and I have a chance to turn this mess
变成互惠互利的约定
into a mutually beneficial arrangement.
伊斯特在这底下 对吧
Esther's down there, isn't she?
你他妈再说她名字试试
Don't you fucking say her name.
好吧
Okay.
你混进了我的家
You conned your way into my family.
这角色是你自己选的
You chose this role,
你就要他妈的演好这个角色
and now you're gonna fucking play it.
梅斯中士 此封邮件附我的请假单 即日起我将休假数日
我休假期间可能不看邮箱和手机
有事请联系莱希警官
祝一切顺利
唐南探长
现在 你可以选择成为伊斯特
So, you can be Esther for now,
过上无数人梦想中的生活
and live a life that anyone would kill to have,
你也可以选择付出代价
or you take the fall for this
戴着手铐被引渡回爱沙尼亚
and get shipped back to Estonia in handcuffs.
怎么样
What do you say?
-很抱歉让你担心了  -对不起 对不起
-I'm sorry I scared you. - I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我们就不该留你一个人
We should have never left you alone.
出什么事了 她骑自行车摔了一跤
What happened?She fell off her bike.
我在路边发现了她
I found her by the side of the road.
亲爱的 你骑自行车干什么
Honey, what are you doing on a bike?
来吧 我们...我们进来暖暖身子
Come here, let's-- let's get warm.
-妈妈 我很抱歉  -打住
-Mom, I'm so sorry. - Stop.
搞什么鬼 是啊
What the fuck?Yeah.
所以 这什么意思
So what does this mean?
意思是她并不是一个孩子
Well, it means she's not a kid.
她是个成年女人 我们可不能低估了她
She is a grown woman and we cannot underestimate her.
不 妈妈 她可不只是个成年女人
No, she's more than that, Mother.
她是个住在我们家的疯子 真该死
She's a psychopath living in our fucking house.
所以我们就只能这样跟她一起生活
So we just have to live with this person?
-我可没这么说  -那我们可不可以直接... 你懂的
I didn't say that.So then, can we just, you know?
让一切看起来像个意外
Make it look like an accident.
为时尚早 我们得考虑一下
It's too soon. We need to think about this.
那现在就任她踩到我们头上
So she just owns us now?
不 不 她和我们平起平坐
No, no, she has just as much to lose as we do.
听着 没人想到会是这样
Look, neither of us were expecting this.
现在 我们就先盯着她
So, for now we just keep an eye on her,
时机到了再把她了结
and when the time is right, we'll end it.
真是疯了 我们也疯了
This is insane, even for us.
好 看到了吗 这就是上膛了
Okay, see that? It's gonna fire.
就像这样 往后拉
Uh-huh.Pull it back. Just like that.
把弓拿好 把箭转过来滑进去
And you get the bow, flip it in, slide it.
-看到了吗 你在看吗  -看着呢
-See this? Are you watching? - Yeah.
好 发射...
Yeah, and you--
真棒
Nice!
-看到了吧  -看到了 太准了
-You see that? - Yeah, yeah.
厉害吧
That's what I'm talking about.
今天我们要去见西格医生
Our meeting with Dr. Segar is today.
你要是没跟鹦鹉说话
A problem we wouldn't have if you hadn't talked
就不会有这个麻烦了
to the parrot.
西德尼是金刚鹦鹉
Sydney was a macaw.Oh.
金刚鹦鹉确实是鹦鹉
All macaws are parrots,
但不是所有鹦鹉都是他妈的金刚鹦鹉
but not all fucking parrots are macaws.
怎么跟西格医生解释
What are we gonna do about that?
她会相信我们的 你和我合作
Oh, we make her believe. Together.
我们的目标是帮伊斯特
DR. SEGAR: One of our goals here is helping Esther acclimate
和家人一起适应新生活
back into life within the family unit.
这需要唤起你们共同的回忆
Part of that is remembering your shared history.
一起度过的欢乐时光
Moments you had, the fun things you did together before.
阿尔布莱特先生 有什么回忆是对你和伊斯特来说
Mr. Albright, what's a memory that means a lot
都意义非凡的
to you and to Esther?
那有太多了
Oh, God, there are so many.
呃 有一次在巴黎过圣诞节
Um, there was Christmas in Paris.
有一年夏天我们去托斯卡纳
The summer in Tuscany.
-还有黄石公园  -对 黄石公园
-Yellowstone. - Yeah, that's up there.
我当时六岁
I was six.
我们看到了熊 有个...有个花栗鼠偷走了我的三明治
We saw bears and a-- a chipmunk stole my sandwich.
是啊 花栗鼠特别多
Oh, my God. There were so many chipmunks.
还有吗 伊斯特 可以具体一点
What else, Esther? Be specific.
我们当时住在麋鹿山牧场 还骑了马
We stayed at Elk Ridge Ranch and rode horses.
我骑的是小矮马 叫小金块
Mine was a pony named Nugget
爸爸骑的马叫斯特奇
and Daddy's horse was called Stretch,
有一次斯特奇低头吃草
and this one time when Stretch leaned down to eat grass,
结果爸爸从马头上摔了下去
Daddy fell right over his head onto the ground.
摔得脸上都是土 牙上也有土
He had dirt all over his face. It was even in his teeth!
你竟然还记得
I can't believe you're telling this story.
而且土在你牙上卡了好多天
Oh, my God. It was in your teeth for days.
总结 伊斯特展现出了健康的人生观
In summary, Esther exhibits a healthy outlook on life,
尤其期待与家人团聚后的生活
especially re-entering into this family unit.
她表现良好
She is highly functioning,
情绪稳定
emotionally well.
结束
That is all.
今天有客人来
There are people coming over today
是来看你的
just to see you.
他们是我们的朋友 而且都认识伊斯特
They're friends of ours who knew Esther.
所以不要瞪人了 好吗
So enough with the glowering, okay?
伊斯特是小淑女
Esther is a lady.
看来不破费是不行了
I think I'm gonna have to do some damage.
很好
Okay.
满载而归
Think we did good.
大家都以为伊斯特回家后肯定变了个人
Everyone expects Esther to be broken.
但圆满结局才是人们所希望的
What they really want is a happy ending.
所以我们要演戏
We are gonna pretend
你最喜欢的颜色是粉色
that pink is your favorite color.
还是天鹅绒的呢
Ooh, velvet.
秘诀是 人们想看到什么 我们就演什么
The secret is to give them a story they want to believe.
这是我最喜欢的一条裙子
This one is my favorite.
你最喜欢的颜色是什么 粉色
What's your favorite color? Pink.
非常非常好
Very, very good.
你说你会画画 你还会什么
Now, you say you can paint. What else can you do?
我非常想念我的家人
I missed my family very much.
能回来太好了
It's lovely to be back.
小淑女 你现在有什么计划呢
And what are your plans now, young lady?
我现在有什么计划呢 妈妈
What are my plans, Mummy?
当然没有
Absolutely nothing.
我不会让你离开我视线一步的
I'm not letting you out of my sight.
我就直说了
So let me get this straight...
你30岁了?
you're 30?
请离开我的房间
Get out of my room now, please.
这不是你的房间 这是我死了的妹妹的房间
It's not your room. It's my dead sister's room.
你不是她 而且你永远都不可能是她
You're not her and you never will be.
-我说得够清楚吗  -滚
-Is that perfectly clear? - Fuck off.
嘴巴放干净点 怪物
Watch your mouth, freak.
现在事情都说开了 我很高兴
You know, I'm glad everything's out in the open now,
我受够了假装接受你属于这里
'cause I'm done pretending like you belong here.
实际上你并不是
You don't.
这是我的房子 我的家人 他们永远不会是你的
This is my house, my family, it'll never be yours.
只要你还在这个屋檐下一天
As long as you're under this roof,
你就要遵守我的规矩
you and I will have an understanding.
那就是
Here's what it is.
我他妈才是踩在你头上的那个人
I fucking own you.
你再扇一次 我就像杀了伊斯特一样杀了你
Do that again and I'll kill you like I killed Esther.
只要我一个电话
One call from me,
你就会滚回那个古拉格
and you're right back in that gulag.
你也不会有好果子吃
You'd go down, too.
为什么 就因为你这个精神病人说的话吗
Why, because of what the illegal immigrant, fugitive,
况且你还是个非法移民的逃犯
mental patient said?
祝你好运咯
Good luck with that.
这里可是美国
This is America.
像我这样的人才有分量
People like me matter,
如果你不是伊斯特的事情被拆穿
and if you're not Esther,
那就是伊斯特再次失踪而已
that just means Esther's missing again.
妈妈对这件事有心病
Mom has a problem with that.
我可没有
I don't.
再见 怪物
See you later, freak.
今晚你会像婴儿一样熟睡的
You are gonna sleep like a fucking baby tonight.
我用迷迭香和橄榄酱做了烤羊腿
I made roast lamb with rosemary and tapenade.
我知道伊斯特不喜欢吃这个
And I know Esther doesn't like it,
所以我做了你最爱的
so I made your favorite.
哦 就像以前一样
Aw, just like the old days.
明天要进城去
I'm really excited about going
我太激动了
into the city tomorrow.
我要给画廊的人看看我这几天的成果
I'm gonna show the gallery what I've been working on.
听起来很棒
That sounds wonderful.
嗯 都是你的功劳
Well, it's all thanks to you.Oh.
我重新找到了以前沉浸于爱好中的快乐
I rediscovered the joy I once felt doing what I love.
我感觉回到了孩童时代 你想一起去吗
I feel like a kid again. You want to come?
我很愿意去
I would love to!
我和伊斯特已经有别的安排了
Oh, Esther and I already have plans.
什么安排
Oh.What plans?
是个惊喜
It's a surprise.
好吧 那我们改天吧
Okay, well, another time then.
爸爸 你又重新开始画画了 真是太好了
It's great that you're painting again, Dad.
嗯 是啊
Well, yeah.
我可以先走了吗
May I be excused?
别忘了你的...
Oh, don't forget your--
你可以拿到楼上吃 没关系的
You can eat upstairs. It's okay.
亲爱的 怎么了
Honey, hey, what's wrong?
爸爸 她没事
Dad, she's fine.
给她一点空间 她没事的
Just give her some space. She's fine.
是的 她可能钢琴弹累了
Yeah, she's probably tired from all that piano playing.
我能进来吗
Can I come in?Mm-hmm.
你还好吗 刚才是怎么回事
Are you okay? What happened down there?
我不喜欢妈妈做的饭
I, uh, I don't really like Mummy's cooking.
告诉你一个秘密
Well, can you keep a secret?
我也不太喜欢
I'm not crazy about it either.
听我说 我喜欢在晚上画画
Well, listen, um, nighttime's my favorite time to paint.
你...你想和我一起吗
You-- you want to come join me?
-好啊  -那楼下见
-Yes, I would love to. - I'll see you downstairs.
这个地方真棒 很高兴你喜欢这里
This is a such a great space.I'm glad you like it.
每个艺术家都需要一个释放内心古怪想法的地方
Every artist needs a space to let their inner weirdo out.
我们要从他人忽视的地方
We get to see beauty and passion
看到美和激情
where others don't even know to look.
我很喜欢这部分
I really like that.
你手上有好多颜料呀
So much paint.
是的 我画画的时候不修边幅
Yeah, I'm a messy painter.
总是惹你妈妈生气
Drives your mother crazy.
我...我今晚就画到这里了
I think I'm-- I think I'm done for the night.
记得关灯
Just turn the lights off.
晚安
Have a good night.
你们两个很开心嘛
Looks like you two had fun.
他说得没错 你很有天赋
He's right, you are talented.
他很不错 不是吗
He is something, isn't he?
你不会傻到以为他想和你在一起吧
Are you so utterly delusional to think that he would want you?
"没想到吧 我不是你女儿"
"Surprise, I'm not your daughter,
"我是个基因突变的骗子"
I'm a mutant grifter."
我觉得大多数男人都会觉得你恶心 他也不会例外
He would be as repulsed by you as I suspect most men are.
不好意思
Well, if you'll excuse me,
我要上楼和我的丈夫做爱了
I'm gonna go upstairs and fuck my husband.
你回来以后 他就变回来了
He really is a new man since you came back.
谢谢你
Thanks for that.
嘿
Hey, you.
我觉得伊斯特不能和我去画廊
I think Esther's really bummed about not coming
所以很不开心
to the gallery with me.
你和伊斯特都会画画
Listen, I love that you and Esther
我很高兴 只是...
have painting in common. I just--
我和她没有这样的共同点
I don't have anything like that with her.
我想和她一起待上一天
I was hoping that I could spend the day with her
或许能找到我们都感兴趣的事情
and maybe we could find something to share.
而且这样你就可以集中精力了 不是更好吗
Plus, it would be good for you to be focused, right?
如果萨尔看了你的画之后很喜欢
I mean, if Sal likes what he sees,
没准你就可以办个画展 重出江湖了
then maybe you get a show and get back out there.
也是我们没有闹得不愉快 对吗
Yeah, okay. We're not hurting, are we?
不 不 一点也不
No, no. Not at all.
你是个出色的画家
You are a great painter.
大家都很想再次看到你的作品
People miss seeing your work.
谢谢
Thank you.
是培根的味道吗
Is that bacon?
简直是天堂
It's heaven.
早上好 爸爸 想要薄饼吗
Good morning, Daddy. Crepe?
好啊 谢谢 你什么都会做呀
Yes, please. Is there anything you can't do?
妈妈要吗
Mummy?
不了 谢谢 我要做我平常喝的...
Oh, no, thanks. I'm gonna make my usual--
奶昔吗
Smoothie?
有希腊酸奶 羽衣甘蓝 亚麻籽 柠檬汁的那种
Greek yogurt, kale, flax seeds, and lemon juice.
都是按照你的喜好做的
Just the way you like it.
尝尝
Try it.
我其实不太饿
I'm not really that hungry.
我喝 拿过来
I'll-- I'll have it. Here.
不 这是专门给妈妈做的
No, this is special just for mummy.
我亲手做的
I made it for you.
宝贝 你真好
Oh, sweetie, that's so nice of you,
但我还是自己做吧
but I prefer to make my own.
特里西亚 尝尝嘛
Tricia, come on. Try it.
很好
Good.
好喝
Mm, delicious.
谢谢
Thank you.
特里西亚 你还好吗 我没事
Tricia, you okay?I'm good.
真的
Yeah?
我知道你很想跟我一起去
I know you wanted to come with me,
但我觉得你跟妈妈在一起
but I think it'll be really good for you to spend the day
对你也好 不过我想给你看个东西
with your mom. I wanted to show you something, though.
这儿
Here.
看中间的那幅
It's the one in the center.
伍德利学校的校长是我的朋友
Dean at Woodley is a friend of mine.
伍德利学校可是全国最好的艺术学校
Woodley is the best art school in the country.
伊斯特 你非常棒 我能把这幅画给他们看看吗
You're scary good, Esther. Can I show it to 'em?
可以 谢谢你
I would love it. Thank you.
你能把这个先带去站台吗
Can you bring this up to the platform?
我去给爸爸妈妈买杯咖啡
I'm just gonna get some coffees for Mom and Dad.
好的 我一会儿去找你
All right, I'll see you up there.
老天 看着路点 孩子
Jesus Christ! Watch where you're going, kid!
-这是你的孩子吗  -是的
-Does she belong to you? - Yes, she does.
怎么了没事 没事
What happened?Oh, nothing. It's fine.
-伊斯特绊倒了  -不好意思 让你等这么久
-Esther tripped. - Sorry, it took forever.
-没事 没事让他们开开眼 好吗  -好的
-No, no! Knock 'em dead, okay? - Yeah.
爸爸 带上我吧
Daddy, take me with you!
宝贝 我也想 下次一定
Oh, honey, I wish. Next time.
再不走就晚了 好吧 晚点见 宝贝
You're gonna miss your train.All right, see you later, honey.
再见
Ciao.
放轻松 妈妈
Easy, Mom.
你他妈以为能杀了我
You think you can fucking kill me?
拿着
Take this.
喝着跟他妈的垃圾一样
Tastes like fucking garbage.
我们的约定到此为止 你他妈的死定了
Our arrangement is over. You're fucking dead.
嘿
Hey!
妈妈 妈妈
Mom! Mom!
妈的 婊子
Fuck! Bitch!
你给我把这该死的门打开 伊斯特
Open the God damn door. Esther!
宝贝 开门
Sweetie, come on.
你敢
Don't you dare!
对不起 我是超速了吗
I'm sorry. Was I driving too fast?
你是伊斯特吧
You must be Esther.
我得去医院看看
I need to go to the hospital.
你没事的
You're fine.
感觉我他妈的被捅了1000刀
Feels like I'm being stabbed a 1,000 fucking times.
-莱希警官  -我的天啊
-Officer Leahy. - Oh, my God.
你能安静两秒钟吗
Can you just be quiet for, like, two seconds?
-怎么了  -我们找到了伊斯特
-What? - We've located Esther.
-是吗  -我正带她回家来
-You did? - I'm bringing her home.
我还通知了艾伦
Oh, and I've informed Allen as well.
好的 再见 操
Okay, bye. Fuck!
没事的 没事的
You're okay. You're okay.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我的天啊
Oh, my goodness. Oh.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
伊斯特回到家以后一直表现得情绪不稳定
Esther's behavior has been so erratic since she got back.
说实话 这段时间很艰难
To be honest, it's been really hard.
她一直撒谎 或者突然发脾气
I mean, there's constant lying and these outbursts of anger.
有时她还开玩笑说要伤害自己
Sometimes she even jokes about hurting herself
可我觉得她不是开玩笑
and I don't think she's really joking.
-你在让她接受治疗吗  -是的 是的
-You have her in therapy? - Yes, yes.
看看谁回来了
Look who's back.
起来 我们现在就动手
Get up. We're doing this. Now.
好啊 到时候了
Well, it's about goddamn time.
操
Fuck.
我受够你了
I am done with you.
这座房子没有值得让你留下的理由了
Nothing is worth having you in this house.
你的自杀会让爸爸心碎
Your suicide is gonna break Daddy's heart,
但他会慢慢淡忘
but he'll get over it.
去死吧 怪胎
Just die, you freak!
她去哪了
Where is she?
我 我 我不是故意的
I-- I-- I didn't mean to.
太棒了
Oh, that's just brilliant.
太突然了
It just happened.
-特里西亚  -嗨 亲爱的
-Tricia. - Hi, honey.
警察给我打了电话
The police just called me.
我知道 我很抱歉 都是我的错
Oh, I know. I'm-- I'm sorry. It was my fault.
伊斯特在商店逛丢了
Esther wandered off at the store,
然后我就 我就慌了
and I just-- I panicked,
-但我找了莱希警官帮忙  -妈妈
-but I called Officer Leahy... - Mom.
他们找到了她
...and they found her.
-那就好  -妈妈
-Oh, good. - Mom.
-好吧 我在火车上了  -什么
-Well, I'm on the train. - What?
-她...  -等等
-She's-- - Hold on.
我现在 正在回家路上
I'm-- I'm coming back home.
我会...
I'll be...
下楼 把她了结了
Go downstairs and finish it.
-什么  -下楼去了结一切
-What? - Go downstairs and finish it.
特里西亚 你还在听吗
Tricia, are you still there?
特里西亚 情况都还好吗
Tricia, is everything okay?
特里西亚 我正在回家的路上
Tricia, I-- I'm coming home now.
-什么  -我正在回家的路上
-What? - I'm coming home.
那你和萨尔的会面怎么办
What about your meeting with Sal?
别管那个了
Forget about that.
别这样 亲爱的 我发誓这里一切都好
No, sweetie. I swear. Everything is fine.
伊斯特回家了 一切正常
Esther is here, all is well.
我已经快到镇上的车站了
Look, I'm almost at the station in town.
那好吧 那你打车回家好吗
Okay, well, can you please take a cab home?
我现在有点走不开
Because I really have my hands full here.
他妈的
Ow, fuck it.
找到你了
There you are.
伊斯特
Esther.
出来吧 伊斯特
Come on out, Esther
不论你他妈的到底是谁
or whatever the fuck your name is.
你知道 我们可以不用这样打打杀杀的
You know, it doesn't have to be like this.
真的吗 贡纳
Really, Gunnar?
我相信我们可以把事情说开的
I'm sure we could figure something out.
你真的这么认为吗
You really believe that?
实话说
Honestly?
不
No.
我也是
Me neither.
妈的
Shit.
贡纳
Gunnar?
不
No.
No!
你干了什么 你干了什么
What have you done? What have you done?
你把一切都毁了
You've taken everything.
艾伦永远不会爱上你的
Allen will never be yours,
但我敢保证 他一定会知道你真正的身份
but I can I promise you this, he will know who you are.
你这个先天畸形的怪胎利用了我们丧女的悲痛
The deformed freak who manipulated our grief,
谋杀了我的儿子 还想要杀我
murdered my son, and tried to kill me.
等我先把你处理掉 我就会这样告诉他
Until I did what had to be done.
叫火警
Call the fire department!
贡纳
Gunnar!
坚持住 我来了
Hold on, I'm coming!
-救命  -爸爸 妈妈要杀了我
-Help! - Daddy, Mommy tried to hurt me!
艾伦 救救我
Allen! Please help!
-艾伦  -别放手
-Allen! - Don't let go!
我坚持不了太久了
I can't hold on much longer.
我快抓不住了
I'm losing my grip!
-爸爸 救我  -宝贝 坚持住 坚持住
-Daddy, help! - Honey, hang on. Hang on!
我来了
I'm coming.
她不是伊斯特 她是个成年女人
She is not Esther! She is a grown woman!
-她在撒谎  -什么
-She's lying! - What?
-她骗了我们  -妈妈在撒谎
-She tricked us! - Mummy's lying!
-把手给我  -不 爸爸 求求你救我
-Give me your hand! - No, Daddy! Please help me!
特里西亚
Tricia!
-这他妈的是什么  -我做这些都是为了你 为了我们
-What the fuck? - I did this for you. For us.
为了我们能在一起 艾伦 我爱你
So we could be together. Allen, I love you.
你到底是谁 你是个怪物
Who the fuck are you? You're a monster!
艾伦
Allen!
这场大火带走了伊斯特的一切
DR. SEGAR: Fire took everything from Esther.
她的家和她的家人
Her home, her family.
这一切都太悲惨了
The whole situation is so tragic.
这太可怕了
It's horrifying.
我知道
I know.
就好像伊斯特受的苦还不够多似的
As if Esther hasn't been through enough already.
之前被诱拐 现在又变成了没人要的孤儿
Abducted and now an orphan with no family to take her in?
那现在怎么办
What will happen now?
我联系了一家很有名的孤儿院
DR. SEGAR: I've reached out to a reputable adoption agency.
我相信我们会给伊斯特找到一个家的
I'm confident we'll find a home
一个能给她应得的关心和爱护的家
where Esther can get the support and love she deserves.
毕竟 谁会不想领养她呢
After all, who wouldn't want to adopt her?